<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<BasicAsset xmlns:md="http://www.movielabs.com/schema/md/v2.3/md" xmlns:ns3="http://www.w3.org/2000/09/xmldsig#" xmlns="http://www.decellc.org/schema/2015/03/coordinator"><BasicData ContentID="urn:dece:cid:eidr-s:1F25-C7FC-9722-5B4A-8A9E-S"><md:UpdateNum>3</md:UpdateNum><md:LocalizedInfo default="false" language="fr"><md:TitleDisplay60>Heros</md:TitleDisplay60><md:TitleSort>Powers Season 01 Episode 05 Heros</md:TitleSort><md:ArtReference resolution="800x1200">https://g.prod.uvvu.com/artwork/a44bf0276dff478db8fa67d2bd56227b</md:ArtReference><md:ArtReference resolution="840x1200">https://g.prod.uvvu.com/artwork/1e5dd443395e420b82aa29ced9c556a8</md:ArtReference><md:ArtReference resolution="96x144">https://g.prod.uvvu.com/artwork/bfcdf8f09d074cc99237645a13002751</md:ArtReference><md:ArtReference resolution="192x288">https://g.prod.uvvu.com/artwork/5c30c2e1a398428aa55d7fb8480774f4</md:ArtReference><md:ArtReference resolution="112x160">https://g.prod.uvvu.com/artwork/0439a2007adc4b44a40aa5f9fd9c1a25</md:ArtReference><md:ArtReference resolution="224x320">https://g.prod.uvvu.com/artwork/dbe1d5854cb54b3ea4a3ca8f8bd76488</md:ArtReference><md:Summary190>Dans le bunker, Walker essaie de résonner Wolfe mais en vain. Entrent alors dans la bataille Triphammer, Zora et Retro Girl qui s'est finalement décidée à quitter l'ouragan Pulp pour ...</md:Summary190><md:Summary400>Dans le bunker, Walker essaie de résonner Wolfe mais en vain. Entrent alors dans la bataille Triphammer, Zora et Retro Girl qui s'est finalement décidée à quitter l'ouragan Pulp pour arrêter Wolfe.</md:Summary400><md:Summary4000>Dans le bunker, Walker essaie de résonner Wolfe mais en vain. Entrent alors dans la bataille Triphammer, Zora et Retro Girl qui s'est finalement décidée à quitter l'ouragan Pulp pour arrêter Wolfe.</md:Summary4000><md:Genre>Drame</md:Genre><md:CopyrightLine>© 2015 Sony Pictures Television Inc. All rights reserved.</md:CopyrightLine></md:LocalizedInfo><md:LocalizedInfo default="true" language="en"><md:TitleDisplay60>Paint It Black</md:TitleDisplay60><md:TitleSort>Powers Season 01 Episode 05 Paint It Black</md:TitleSort><md:ArtReference resolution="800x1200">https://g.prod.uvvu.com/artwork/4db36885e76c414c83c18a6979061c0c</md:ArtReference><md:ArtReference resolution="840x1200">https://g.prod.uvvu.com/artwork/62ed10c1669d4fd4a80db719c55efce7</md:ArtReference><md:ArtReference resolution="96x144">https://g.prod.uvvu.com/artwork/306e50031f4f4d0986204d177ce73f9f</md:ArtReference><md:ArtReference resolution="192x288">https://g.prod.uvvu.com/artwork/b18f9a2848f8415db9cbfc279b64c7c7</md:ArtReference><md:ArtReference resolution="112x160">https://g.prod.uvvu.com/artwork/866b94bc40e4440dbd5deb70dac28e40</md:ArtReference><md:ArtReference resolution="224x320">https://g.prod.uvvu.com/artwork/80c3df4e10bb45b58929e59bee2fdab6</md:ArtReference><md:Summary190>As he rides out some Sway-induced flashbacks to a gruesome massacre in 1994 when he and Royalle were coming into their own, Walker comes face-to-face with Wolfe inside The Shaft. Knowing ...</md:Summary190><md:Summary400>As he rides out some Sway-induced flashbacks to a gruesome massacre in 1994 when he and Royalle were coming into their own, Walker comes face-to-face with Wolfe inside The Shaft. Knowing that Triphammer and the Powers Division are looking for him, Wolfe insists they run. As the press is assembling outside to report on the chaos, Wolfe persuades Walker to find a way out. Unaware that Triphammer ...</md:Summary400><md:Summary4000>As he rides out some Sway-induced flashbacks to a gruesome massacre in 1994 when he and Royalle were coming into their own, Walker comes face-to-face with Wolfe inside The Shaft. Knowing that Triphammer and the Powers Division are looking for him, Wolfe insists they run. As the press is assembling outside to report on the chaos, Wolfe persuades Walker to find a way out. Unaware that Triphammer has already installed The Drainer, Royalle teleports into Wolfe's cell intent on protecting his source of Sway - and is left helpless when the device saps his powers. With Triphammer closing in fast, Wolfe devours a pair of prisoners and absorbs their powers. When Wolfe demands to know what's become of him in the years since he was a formidable Power, Walker shoots him. Though the bullet has no impact and Wolfe gets control of the gun, Walker still tries to take his powers back. But before the transfer is complete, Triphammer bursts in to stop him. Meanwhile, as the reporters gathered outside interview Zora, Retro Girl insists on continuing to help the hurricane victims instead of going to The Shaft. Unwilling to wait, Zora heads inside where Wolfe and Triphammer are engaged in mortal combat. After besting Triphammer, Wolfe tells Walker that he has no powers left to return. When Walker grabs him to continue the transfer, Wolfe musters all his strength and strikes back, but hits Zora instead. As reporter Collette McDaniels reflects on the many massacres that have increased Wolfe's powers, Retro Girl arrives, launching into Wolfe as he is about to kill Zora. Though able to interrupt the assault, she's exhausted following her hurricane rescue. When Wolfe sinks his teeth into Retro Girl, Zora recovers enough to fight him off. But after Wolfe lands a near fatal blow and returns to feed on Retro Girl, Walker musters the strength to stop him. Driving Wolfe through the floor, Walker lands outside the cell where Royalle is incapacitated. Wolfe continues to fight back until Walker</md:Summary4000><md:Genre>Drama</md:Genre><md:CopyrightLine>© 2015 Sony Pictures Television Inc. All rights reserved.</md:CopyrightLine></md:LocalizedInfo><md:LocalizedInfo default="false" language="de"><md:TitleDisplay60>Violett ist das neue Schwarz</md:TitleDisplay60><md:TitleSort>Powers Staffel 01 Episode 05 Violett ist das neue Schwarz</md:TitleSort><md:ArtReference resolution="800x1200">https://g.prod.uvvu.com/artwork/d12d7d0f2f6d4617ba45cc1d2ba213e4</md:ArtReference><md:ArtReference resolution="840x1200">https://g.prod.uvvu.com/artwork/eac802f008744718907f341730bc66e2</md:ArtReference><md:ArtReference resolution="96x144">https://g.prod.uvvu.com/artwork/f85458f6f1424dbab27f9fe7932844e2</md:ArtReference><md:ArtReference resolution="192x288">https://g.prod.uvvu.com/artwork/132a272ffb4e4b6b95597e90e0989da7</md:ArtReference><md:ArtReference resolution="112x160">https://g.prod.uvvu.com/artwork/9ecd49c222824327b717485b29199341</md:ArtReference><md:ArtReference resolution="224x320">https://g.prod.uvvu.com/artwork/822b8a3ad4124b108552ecdb10c0c919</md:ArtReference><md:Summary190 cast="true">Retro Girl und Zora (Michelle Forbes, Logan Browning) sind zur Stelle, um den gefährlichen Wolfe (Eddie Izzard) an der Flucht zu hindern. Doch Walker (Sharlto Copley) merkt bald, dass er ...</md:Summary190><md:Summary400 cast="true">Retro Girl und Zora (Michelle Forbes, Logan Browning) sind zur Stelle, um den gefährlichen Wolfe (Eddie Izzard) an der Flucht zu hindern. Doch Walker (Sharlto Copley) merkt bald, dass er sich Wolfe allein stellen muss, da er noch eine alte Rechnung mit ihm offen hat.</md:Summary400><md:Summary4000 cast="true">Retro Girl und Zora (Michelle Forbes, Logan Browning) sind zur Stelle, um den gefährlichen Wolfe (Eddie Izzard) an der Flucht zu hindern. Doch Walker (Sharlto Copley) merkt bald, dass er sich Wolfe allein stellen muss, da er noch eine alte Rechnung mit ihm offen hat.</md:Summary4000><md:Genre>Drama</md:Genre><md:CopyrightLine>© 2015 Sony Pictures Television Inc. All rights reserved.</md:CopyrightLine></md:LocalizedInfo><md:RunLength>PT1H0M0.000S</md:RunLength><md:ReleaseYear>2015</md:ReleaseYear><md:ReleaseDate>2015-07-14</md:ReleaseDate><md:WorkType>Episode</md:WorkType><md:RatingSet><md:Rating><md:Region><md:country>FR</md:country></md:Region><md:System>CNC</md:System><md:Value>T</md:Value></md:Rating><md:Rating><md:Region><md:country>DE</md:country></md:Region><md:System>FSK</md:System><md:Value>12</md:Value></md:Rating><md:Rating><md:Region><md:country>GB</md:country></md:Region><md:System>BBFC</md:System><md:Value>18</md:Value></md:Rating></md:RatingSet><md:SequenceInfo><md:Number>5</md:Number></md:SequenceInfo><md:Parent relationshipType="isepisodeof"><md:ParentContentID>urn:dece:cid:eidr-s:79FD-21E0-E7BA-7A63-87DB-S</md:ParentContentID></md:Parent></BasicData><ResourceStatus><Current CreatedBy="urn:dece:org:org:dece:sonypicturesentertainment:contentprovider" CreationDate="2015-09-08T20:45:53.040Z" ModificationDate="2017-10-31T03:11:03.798Z" ModifiedBy="urn:dece:org:org:dece:sonypicturesentertainment:contentprovider"><Value>urn:dece:type:status:active</Value></Current></ResourceStatus></BasicAsset>